Thank you for waiting.
お待たせ
It was hot today.
暑かったね、今日ね
Why don't you have a drink?
なんか、ちょっと飲まない?
recovery.
回復
Oh, that's nice.
ああ、いいですね
It's been a while.
久しぶりですね
久しぶりです
It's beautiful, Karazu.
綺麗だね、からず
thank you.
ありがとう
Is everything okay now?
もう先は大丈夫なの?
When you get home, don't you think it smells like alcohol?
帰って、なんかアルコール臭いねとかって言われない?
No, it's okay.
いや、大丈夫
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
What is it today?
今日は何?
What are you getting for your husband?
旦那さんに何つってきてる?
Drinking party with friends.
友達と飲み会
Are you meeting for drinks?
飲み会ってきてるんだ?
Well then, okay?
じゃあ、いいか
I didn't think he would invite me again.
また、なんか誘って来ると思わなかった
I took a photo before.
前、撮影したったじゃん
For some reason, he hated it so much that I thought he wouldn't come.
なんか、結構嫌がってたからさ、来ないかと思ってた
I want to take a photo today too, is that okay?
今日もさ、撮影したいんだけど、いい?
Huh?
あれ?
誰?
I agree.
そうだね
Well, I get nervous if I don't have my camera with me.
なんかさ、カメラ持ってないと、うち緊張してるんだよね
Not much because I'm not used to it.
慣れてないから、あまり
My face isn't that bright.
顔とかあんまつらないから
If you feel tired.
顔つらんなら
Yeah, it's boring.
うん、つらない
It's boring.
つらないよ
You don't like meat, right?
肉嫌いなんでしょ?
I hate meat.
肉嫌い
Eat this.
これ食べ
Okay.
よし
What is it today?
今日は何?
Have you made dinner?
夜ご飯作ってきた?
With my husband.
旦那さんちゃんと
What did you make?
何作ったの?
With hamburger.
ハンバーグと
Hamburger?
ハンバーグ?
Looks like an old man.
おごさまみたいだな
With hamburger.
ハンバーグと
soup.
スープ
My husband is also a drinker.
旦那さんも酒飲みな
Huh?
えっ?
My husband is also a drinker.
旦那さんも酒飲みな
I drink a lot of alcohol.
酒めっちゃ飲みな
It smells really good.
めっちゃいい匂いしてる
Do you drink a lot?
結構飲む?
Yes, drink in moderation.
うん、ほどほど飲む
It smells really good, Triple.
めっちゃ匂いするね、トリプル
Very triple.
めっちゃトリプル
Is it okay if I fill you inside now?
今から中とかいっぱいするのに、大丈夫?
Even though it's full inside, let me smell this.
中とかいっぱいするのに、この匂いさせて
Will it change?
変化する?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
So, can we go to the hotel?
じゃあ、ホテル行っていい?
It smelled really bad.
めっちゃ臭かった
Let's be very careful.
いっぱい注意しちゃおう
What should I do?
どうすよ
Are you still nervous?
まだ緊張してますか?
Please stand for a moment.
ちょっと立ってください
This is a very high point for me personally.
これね、個人的にポイント超高いんですけど
I like small children.
ちっちゃい子好きなんですよ
ちっちゃい子好き
47 cm.
47センチ
I'm not with my uncle either.
おじさんともいません
This outfit is cute.
可愛いね、この服
Do you regret getting married?
結婚したこと、後悔したりする?
I haven't.
してない
Haven't you?
して ない?
Do you like your husband?
旦那さん好き?
Do you like it?
好きなんですか?
But it's like I can't satisfy my sexual desire.
でも性欲満たせないから、みたいな
He seems to be behaving suspiciously.
挙動不審なそうですよ
I'm acting suspicious now.
今 挙動不審になってる
Suspicious behavior.
挙動不審
I don't know why this is.
どうしてか分かんないよね、これはね
It seems obvious.
当たり前そうです
Why are you laughing like this?
なんでこうやって笑うの?
Do you laugh like this?
こうやって笑うの?
close.
近い
It's different for a position like this.
こんな地位に違う
Even if you walk right away.
すぐに歩いても
Wow, it's purple today.
うわ、今日紫なんだ
It's a fascinating color.
魅惑の色だね
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Do you know what that is?
何それか分かる?
tickles.
くすぐったい
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
Doesn't it feel good?
気持ちいいんじゃないの?
This tickles.
くすぐったいな、これ
Look.
ほ ら
It's so beautiful, really.
なんか綺麗だよね、めっちゃ
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Facing blue, facing blue.
青向いて、青向いて
Look nice.
綺麗に向いて
Are you going to do something yourself?
自分で何とかするの?
I've never lost it.
しなくしたことない
Does this feel good?
これ気持ちいい?
How good does it feel?
どれくらい気持ちいい?
How does it feel to have your butts lined up?
お尻が並べられたどっちの気持ち?
Rabbit.
うさつき
How do you like to be touched?
どんな風に触られるのが好き?
It tickles and it feels good.
くすぐった気持ちいいんだよ
That's kind of great.
なんか偉い
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいい
Facing this way.
こっちの向いて